Guide to the Jake Austen Zine Collection 1972-2013
University of Chicago Library
- Walters, Britton (editor), Moo juice megazine, 17, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 4, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 5, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 6, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 7, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 8, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 9, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 11, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 12, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 13, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 14, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 15, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 16, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 17, November 2002 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 18, April 2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 20, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 24, April 2010 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Norman, Motorcycho, 25, April 2011 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Cronin, Colleen, Mouth and eyes and heart all bleed, 5, "February 22, 1995", Inscribed by the author to Jake Austen (Box 17, Folder 14)
- McMahon, David, The muckraker, 4 - South Bend, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
- McMahon, David, The muckraker, 5 - Landscape for an American, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
- McMahon, David, The muckraker, 6 - Oakland, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Palonen, Timo, Muuna Takeena, 4, 1997? (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Palonen, Timo, Muuna Takeena, 6, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Marr, John, Murder can be fun, 14, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Vrusho, Spike (editor), Murtaugh, 9, undated, Has laid in a note from the author to Jake Austen dated April 6, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Vrusho, Spike (editor), Murtaugh, 10, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Vrusho, Spike (editor), Murtaugh, 13, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Musea, 24, August 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Mutant renegade zine, 5 - The sex issue, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Mutant renegade zine, 11 - The sell out issue, Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Mutant renegade zine, 13 - the millennium issue, Winter 2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Simpson, Linda (editor-in-chief), My comrade, 10, Summer 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, 0, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -1, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -3, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -4, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -5, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -6, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -7, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My fat Irish ass!: the official fanzine of the assbeaters, -8, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- My own cum masturbazine, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Mystery date, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Goldstein, Chauncy (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 2, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Goldstein, Chauncy (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Erman, Crisp (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 4, May 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Strohmeyer, Karl (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 5, Late May 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Erman, Crisp (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 6, July 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Erman, Crisp (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 7, August 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Strohmeyer, Karl (editor-in-chief), Narc!, 8, September 2005 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Erman, Crisp (publisher), Narc!, 9, March 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Erman, Crisp (publisher), Narc!, 10, May 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Narcolepsy press review, 1, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
- "Nets "word"!: the voice of the New Jersey Nets fans, "December 2, 1992" (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Hensley, Kirby J., The news, "vol. 36, issue 4, Summer II 1998 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Newshole, 4, October/November 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Node pajomo: a contact zine in the spirit of global mail, Spring 2009 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- No duh, 1 - Juliana Lueckling, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
- "No shirt, no shoes, no service, 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
- "No shirt, no shoes, no service, 4, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
- No time, "vol. 1, issue 1, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Eldridge, Kevin, Not your nightmare, 4, May/June 1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Eldridge, Kevin, Not your nightmare, 5, September/October 1995 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Obscure publications, 31, July 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Obscure publications, 32, September 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Obvious crap: the newsletter, 10, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Mizelle, Brett, Okey dokey, 2, November 1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Mizelle, Brett, Okey dokey, Mini, December 1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Mizelle, Brett, Okey dokey, 4, Winter 1995, Has laid in a Topps baseball card of Greg McMichael (Box 18, Folder 17)
- The old school beat, 3, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
- McIllwraith, Angus, 101 contradictions in the Bible, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Open mike, 2, Summer 1993 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Opera dog, 4, Winter 1999/2000 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Kaldenberg, Wyatt (publisher), Pagan revival, 41, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Pajomo, 1, 2007? (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Pants that don't fit, 5, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Farseth, Erik, "Paper, scissors, clocks: a journal of cultural revolution, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Farseth, Erik, "Paper, scissors, clocks: a journal of cultural revolution, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Farseth, Erik, "Paper, scissors, clocks: a journal of cultural revolution, 3, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Mitchell, John E.; Christy, Jana, Pardon my appearance, 1, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Sarah-Katherine, Pasty, undated, Inscribed by the author, dated December 19, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Nixon, Linda, Patience enterprise, 16, April 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Nixon, Linda, Patience enterprise, 19, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Peaches and herbicide, 3, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Gnade, Adam (editor), The perfect mix tape segue, 5 - Sickness and health, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Perry's old time videos, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Davis, Jodi; Herschelman, Tina; Lorimer, Sara; Schuster, Paul, Pinto, 1, February and March 1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- V., M. Trillby, Plaintive wombat gazette, "no. 1, vol. 1, January/February 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 1, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 2, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 3, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 4 - The long-awaited music issue!, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 5, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 6, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 7, 1997, Has stapled in Plotz Lite, Issue 3: Guide to circumcision (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 8 - Jews in Hollywood!, undated, Has stapled in Plotz Lite, Issue 5: My favorite mensch--Ben Stiller! (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz: the zine for the vaclempt, 11, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Plotz lite, 1 - Yiddish to go!, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Frazier, Gordon (editor), Pluck, 4, Fall 1993, Has laid in an advertisement for the North American Jew's Harp Festival, July 29, 30, and 31, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Kulik, Missy, Pocket, 1 - Interview issue, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Kulik, Missy, Pocket, 5, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Pop stock, 3, July 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Pop stock, 4, September 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 3, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 4, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 5, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 6, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 7, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 8, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 786, no. 9, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Poe, Susan, Popular reality special report, "vol. 787, no. 2, January 2010 or so (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Fright, Wred, The pornographic flabbergasted emus, 5, June 2003, Has handwritten note from the author laid in, dated June 22, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Fright, Wred, The pornographic flabbergasted emus, 7, September 2003 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Scavone, Jeff (editor/publisher), Powerbunny 4x4, 8, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Rodgers, Jason, Psionic plastic joy, 14, July 2009 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Rodgers, Jason, Psionic plastic joy, 16, Fall 2010 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Rodgers, Jason, Psionic plastic joy, 17, Fall 2012 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Marszewski, Ed (editor/publisher; Marszewski, Rachael (publisher), PR: a proximity publication, 1, Spring 2009 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Rayson, Anthony, "Prisoner zines: solidarity conference workshop, Penn State, April 7th, 2001, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- STAND: shut this airport nightmare down, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Rayson, Anthony, Nursery rhymes for global crimes, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Aull, Matthew, A privileged look at prisons: a reflection of a prison visit from the eyes of a middle class college student, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Profane existence mailorder distribution catalog, 4, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Profane existence, 17, October/November 1992 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- MZA (editor); Sun (editor), Pro-teen, 1, May 2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Rufolo, Peter; Rufolo, Greg, Pro wrestling monthly, March 1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Marszewski, Ed (editor/publisher; Marszewski, Rachael (editor/publisher), Proximity, 4 - The remedies issue, Spring 2009 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Psyche out, The last issue, Autumn 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Bogard, Seth, Puberty strike, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Bogard, Seth, Puberty strike presents psycho #1 fan!!!, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Minsker, Ethan, Psycho moto zine, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Minsker, Ethan, Psycho moto zine, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Minsker, Ethan, Psycho moto zine, 6, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Minsker, Ethan, Psycho moto zine, 11, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Minsker, Ethan, Psycho moto zine, 12, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- PTBH!, "no. 4, pt. 1, Spring 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- PTBH!, "no. 4, pt. 2, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
- PTBH!, 5, Summer/Fall 1998 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- PTBH!, 10, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Pukka joint massif, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Punk life, 25, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Pulled mints, 2, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Pulled mints, 3, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Yates, John, Punchline, 4, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Yates, John, Punchline, 13, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Wallace, G., Quack with me, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Rowland, Avalokitesvara, Q.U.E.E.R zine, 1, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Rowland, Avalokitesvara, Q.U.E.E.R zine, 3, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Abeyta, Edith, Quench: a beverage zine, 1, undated, Has envelope (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Quitter quarterly, 1, Winter 1994 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Wheeler, Tom (editor/publisher), Rabble review, Summer 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 1, Spring 1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 2, Summer 1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 3, Fall 1996 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 4, Winter 1996/1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 5, Spring 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 6, Summer 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 7, Fall 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 8, September 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Bob, Raccoon times, 10, April 1998 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Moniz, Tomas (editor), Rad dad, 18, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Moniz, Tomas (editor), Rad dad, 19, "February 15, 2011" (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Moniz, Tomas (editor), Rad dad, 20, "July 15, 2011" (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Moniz, Tomas (editor), Rad dad, 21, "March 1, 2011" (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Radical cheerleader handbook, 3, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Random individuals, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- X, Ray, X-rayer, 4, January 1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Byzewski, Michael J. (editor/designer), Readyset…aesthetic, 2, Winter 2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Real fun!, 1, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Red pop revenge, 3, Spring 1995 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Reality, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Rayson, Anthony, Report to the Evironmental Law & Policy Center for 2001, 2001? (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Jaz, Kat (editor); McNeeley, Mike (associate editor), Reptiles of the mind, 35, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Raz, Katherine, Retail whore, 3, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Raz, Katherine, Retail whore, 5 - The identity crisis issue, November 2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Raz, Katherine, Retail whore, 6- Mixtape issue, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Raz, Katherine, Retail whore, 7 - The stalking issue, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Raz, Katherine, Retail whore, 8 - The car issue, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Rinso fanzine, 1, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Rinso fanzine, 3, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Rinso fanzine, 4, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Riverside art scene, A1 - split zine with Artzine, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Riverside art scene, 4, June 1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Riverside art scene, Mid-1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Riverside art scene, 20, October 2003 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Frank, David, Rocks and blows, 3, July 2006 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Lennard, Dann, Rogue, 1, February 2012 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Rope apple, 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Carver, Lisa, Rollerderby, 9, Winter 1992 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Carver, Lisa, Rollerderby, 14, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- A rough guide to bicycle maintenance, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 1, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 2, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 3, "March 12, 1992" (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 4, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 5, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 6, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 7, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 8, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 9, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 10, "July 10, 1992" (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 11, "August 22, 1992" (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 12, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 13, "October 10, 1992" (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 14, "November 17, 1992" (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Haeg, Mike, Rump, 15 - Special humiliation issue!, "December 10, 1992" (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Johnson, Tim, Mort Clowney Jr., 5, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Rustbelt, 360, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Harvick, Ben, Salsa amoeba, 2, "January 23, 1995" (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Sanimag, 3, May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Von Kizer, Denise Dawes, Sardine, 3, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Von Kizer, Denise Dawes, Sardine, 5, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Scab city, 4, March 20 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Scab city, 5, March 22 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Allen, Mark (editor), Scam, 9, Fall 2012 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Allen, Mark (editor), Scam, 11, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Allen, Mark (editor), Scam, 12, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Allen, Mark (editor), Scam lite, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Garcia, Krista, The scaredy-cat stalker, 3, Almost spring 1996 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Garcia, Krista, The scaredy-cat stalker, 5, Winter 1996/1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Garcia, Krista, The scaredy-cat stalker, 6, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Garcia, Krista, The scaredy-cat stalker, 7, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
- "Scenezine: music, news, and arts monthly, 13, February 1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- The secondhand, 1, February 2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 3, Fall 2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 4, Winter 2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 5, Spring 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 7, Winter 2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 16, Winter 2005 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 18, Fall 2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- The secondhand, 19, Winter 2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Koo, Sung Mo, Secret Asian man, "vol. 1, no. 1, February 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Koo, Sung Mo, Secret Asian man, "vol. 1, no. 2, June 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Cornell, Andy, The secret files of Captain Sissy, 5, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
- The secret hand signals of the DBA, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Selfetseam queen, 2 - Family values, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Booth, Gene; Tran, Grace, Sensation, 1, June 2011 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Shake!, 1, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Shelf life, 1, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Shelf life, 3, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Shelf life, 4, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Shotgun seamstress, 2, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Shotgun seamstress, 6, September 2011 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Robnoxious, Shut up and love the rain, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Radio signals, 2, September 2013 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- DJ Frederick, Signals, 4, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
- DJ Frederick, Signals, 5, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Silencio magazine, 1 - Summer issue, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Silhouette, "vol. 67, no. 5, January 1992, Has manuscript annotations from Missy Kulik throughout (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Silhouette, "vol. 67, no. 6, March 1992 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Silhouette, "vol. 68, no. 4, January 1994, Has manuscript annotations from Missy Kulik throughout (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Skels life, 10, February 1991 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Skate my mattress, 1, 1993? (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Slack, 9, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Empress; Starlette, Slander zine, 2, May/June 1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Empress; Starlette, Slander zine, 3, July/August 1998, Is no. 49 of 100 copies (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Empress; Starlette, Slander zine, 4, January/February/March 1999 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Asher, Matt (editor/publisher), The Chicago scroll, "vol. 1, issue 5, "July 11, 1995" (Box 22, Folder 21)